(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
もこもこ...
Fluffy fluffy...
ねむたい...
I'm sleepy...
ちょこ、ねむたい...
Choco is sleepy...
ちょこ...
Choco...
待て待て待て待て！
Wait wait wait wait!
こっち？
This way?
やだやだやだやだ！
No no no no!
どうも、ホロライブ二期生悪魔のバーチャル保健医、癒月ちょこです。
Hello, I'm Hololive 2nd Gen's devilish virtual school nurse, Yuzuki Choco.
お前何しとんじゃ！
What the heck are you doing!
Thank you Superchat, thank you very much.
ほら、豚、登って！頑張って、豚！
Come on, pig, climb! Do your best, pig!
ほら、豚。こっちよこっち。どっち？
Come on, pig. This way, over here. Which way?
はいはいはいはい。
Yes yes yes yes.
なんだろう。
I wonder what it is.
何年やってると思ってるんですか？ええ？
How many years do you think I've been doing this? Huh?
先生に向かって何ですかその言葉遣いは！
What kind of language is that towards a teacher!
友達じゃないんですよ！いいですか？
We're not friends! You got that?
癒月ちょこ「先生」だからね。
It's Yuzuki Choco "Sensei", okay.
お、やばい！うわああ！
Oh, crap! Whoaaa!
おいしかったの...
It was delicious...
あ、違う！だめ！
Ah, no! Stop!
ちょこしかおらん。
Only Choco is here.
なんか動いた！
Something moved!
なんだあいつ！
What is that thing!
はい、いらっしゃいませ～。
Yes, welcome~.
ちょこ二期生だよ。
Choco is 2nd Gen.
二期生。
2nd Gen.
なぁ～
Naa~
おやすみ...
Good night...
ん... おいし。
Mm... delicious.
ふわ～いい天気
Ah~ what nice weather.
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したーい
I want to take a nap on the infirmary bed.
ズル休み許されない
Slacking off isn't allowed.
保健室は神聖なの
The infirmary is sacred.
サボってる？調査だけ
Slacking off? Just investigating.
誰も来なきゃやる気でない
I'm not motivated if no one comes.
Choco Choco Sensation Yay!
Choco Choco Sensation!
このままじゃ私ダメみたい
It seems I'll be useless like this.
あー起きなきゃ不登校だから
Ah, I gotta wake up or it's truancy.
2回めのあくびおやすみなさい
A second yawn, goodnight.
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
少しだけ寝かせて
Just let me sleep a little.
先生モードシャットダウン
Teacher mode shutdown.
夢みるふわふわ
Dreaming fluffy fluffy.
ずっとこうして眠りたーい
I want to sleep like this forever.
ありがとう
Thank you.
ぽかぽか
Warm and fuzzy.
今日特殊欠席だけ
Just a special absence today.
油断大敵ね
Carelessness is a great enemy.
急に君が来るなんて
To think you'd come suddenly.
ねぇどこか悪いの？
Hey, is something wrong?
何かを期待しているのかな？
Are you expecting something?
ゆらぐ心めぐる感情
Wavering heart, swirling emotions.
くちどけ甘いSensation
Melt-in-your-mouth sweet Sensation.
癒されたい甘えていたい
Want to be healed, want to be spoiled.
頼ってよChoco Sensation
Rely on me, Choco Sensation.
君の視線君の体温
Your gaze, your body heat.
分かっても恋は測れない
Even if I understand, love cannot be measured.
元気なのにため息しちゃう
Sighing even though you're healthy.
もしかして何かの病？
Could it be some kind of illness?
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart pounds.
トキメキ運んできてMy Student
Bring me the excitement, My Student.
ズル休み
Playing hooky,
また来たの？
you came again?
保健室は神聖なの
The infirmary is sacred.
サボってた？
Were you slacking?
調査だけ
Just investigating.
やっぱり君にいてほしい
Actually, I want you here.
明日は週末！
Tomorrow is the weekend!
おやすみ！
Goodnight!
なんだよ！
What the heck!
家飲み！
Drinking at home!
最高！
The best!
引きこもり！
Shut-in life!
最高！
The best!
もちろんノーメイク！
Of course, no makeup!
チャイムが鳴ったら白衣着ます！
When the chime rings, I'll put on my lab coat!
さぁすべてを見せて
Now, show me everything.
ちゃんと診断できないじゃん
I can't diagnose you properly otherwise.
何を隠してるの
What are you hiding?
鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
I can hear your heartbeat's speed.
見せて心めくるシャツを
Show me your heart, flipping up the shirt.
正常保てる？Danger Zone
Can you keep it normal? Danger Zone.
愛されたい頼られたい
Want to be loved, want to be relied on.
かまってよChoco Sensation
Pay attention to me, Choco Sensation.
君の重み君の匂い
Your weight, your scent.
分かっても愛は測れない
Even if I understand, love cannot be measured.
大好きだからため息しちゃう
I sigh because I love you so much.
やっぱりそれは恋の病
After all, that is lovesickness.
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart pounds.
トキメキ運んできてMy Student
Bring me the excitement, My Student.
魔界だってこの世界だって
Even in the demon world, even in this world.
みんな癒しが必要だから
Because everyone needs healing.
Choco Choco Sensation Yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい！
I definitely want to ruin you too!
揺らぐ心巡る感情
Wavering heart, swirling emotions,
口どけ甘いセンセーション
A melting sweet sensation.
癒されたい 甘えていたい
Want to be healed, want to be spoiled,
頼ってよ ちょこせんせーしょん
Rely on me, Choco-sensei-tion.
君の視線 君の体温
Your gaze, your body heat,
分かっても恋は測れない
Even if I know, love can't be measured.
元気なのにダメージしちゃう
Even though I'm fine, I take damage,
もしかしてもう手遅れ
Maybe it's already too late.
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart pounds,
ドキドキ運んで 来て！毎週です！
Come bring the heartbeats! Every week!
ちょこちょこ せんせーしょん イェイ！
Choco Choco Sensation Yeah!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to ruin you too.
はーい！ということで...
Okaaaay! So...
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026！始まりましたー！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Festival 2026 has started!
見て見て！一曲目からちょこ...
Look, look! From the first song, Choco...
生まれ変わりました！
Has been reborn!
いや今日はね、原点回帰ということで...
Well today, it's about returning to origins, so...
ちょこの なんと！保健室ステージなの！
It's Choco's... surprisingly! Infirmary stage!
いやちょっと 保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって、めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりました！
Well, the infirmary has also been reborn a bit and became super cute!
シチュエーションドラマとかできそうだよね？
Looks like we could do situation dramas, right?
今日は生まれ変わったニューちょこと...
Today, with the reborn New Choco...
素敵なゲスト様をいっぱい呼んでライブをしていくんだけど...
...I've invited many wonderful guests to perform a live, but...
その前に、みんなちょこのこと...
Before that, everyone...
もっと見たいよね？
...wants to see more of Choco, right?
あ、でも まだダメだよ。
Ah, but not yet.
これから来る お二人に...
To the two people coming now...
ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいました！
...I've requested a Choco photo session!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう。
So let's call them out right away.
ノエル様ー！ラミィ様ー！
Noel-sama! Lamy-sama!
ああああーー！
Aaaah!
来たよー！
We're here!
せーの！ちょこ先生...
One, two! Choco-sensei...
お誕生日おめでとうー！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうー！嬉しいー！
Thank you! I'm happy!
ということで今回はね、この可愛い両手に花で、可愛いお二人に...
So this time, with these cute flowers in both hands, these two...
ちょっとね ちょこの撮影会をしてってもらおうと思うんですけど...
...I'm thinking of having them do a Choco photo session, but...
まずは自己紹介よろしくお願いします。ノエちゃんから。
First, self-introductions please. Starting with Noe-chan.
あい！こんまっするー！ホロライブ三期生の白銀ノエルと！
Aye! Kon-muscle! Hololive 3rd Gen, Shirogane Noel, and!
はーい！ホロライブ五期生の顔が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
Yes! Hololive 5th Gen's 'My Face is a Liver', Yukihana Lamy!
今日はよろしくお願いします！
Please treat us well today!
まぁね ちょっとちょこ先生の本当に可愛くなったところ...
Well, Choco-sensei has really become cute...
ちょっと団長頑張って攻めていこうと思いますのでよろしくお願いします。
The Captain will do her best to attack, so please look forward to it.
攻めちゃって攻めちゃって！
Attack me, attack me!
ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
Lamy also wants to attack the limits!
いや撮影会やるならちょっとね、このお二人を呼ぶしかないかなと思って呼んじゃいました！
If I'm doing a photo session, I thought I had no choice but to call these two!
嬉しいー！
I'm happy!
いやしかもしかも、ちょっと後でこの三人から...
And, and! A bit later, from us three...
なんとお知らせもあるみたいなので！
There seems to be an announcement!
まぁ撮影会の後で皆様楽しみにしといてください！
Well, please look forward to it after the photo session!
それじゃちょっとこちらで撮影会よろしくお願いします。
Then, please do the photo session over here.
行くぞー！
Let's go!
え？は？え？は？
Eh? Ha? Eh? Ha?
何かすごいとこ来たぞ！
We came to an amazing place!
ええすごい！可愛い！
Eh amazing! Cute!
可愛いでしょ可愛いでしょ？
Cute right? Cute right?
撮影会はちょこのここの診察室でやります！
We'll do the photo session in Choco's infirmary here!
やったー診察室だー！
Yay! It's the infirmary!
ちょこ先の診察室ー！
Choco-sen's infirmary!
いいでしょ～？
It's nice, right?
いいでしょ～！
It is nice!
でもさ、診察室だけど…ベ、ベッドは？
But, it's an examination room... w-where's the bed?
ベッドどこ？
Where's the bed?
なんかパネルもあるけど…あれ使う？
There's a panel over there... are we using that?
とんでもないものがあるけど…
There's something outrageous over there...
え、これダメなの？
Eh, is that no good?
そこは後のメン限で使うの！
I'm using that later for the Members-only stream!
なに！？
What?!
メン限で！？
Members-only?!
メン限で！
Members-only!
そう、ちょっとね、ベッドとか…
So, with the bed and all...
ちょっと色々撮影会とか、シチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなって。
I was thinking of doing a photoshoot or a situation drama.
シチュエーションドラマ！？
Situation drama?!
とんでもないことをしようとしてる！
She's trying to do something outrageous!
本当にだよ！
Seriously!
いや、そうなんですよ～。
Well, that's right~.
ま、それは置いといて！
Well, let's put that aside!
あ、置いとくんだ。
Ah, we're putting it aside.
ちょっと今回は二人に撮影をしてもらいたいので、
This time, I want you two to take photos for me,
まずは…！
so first...!
分かりました！
Understood!
撮りますよ～！
I'll take them~!
ラミィ様には…
For Lamy-sama...
カメラを！
A camera!
え、本格的な！
Wow, it's a professional one!
すごい！カメラ来たー！
Amazing! A camera appeared!
そしてノエル様にはこちらの、じゃじゃーん！
And for Noel-sama, this right here... Ta-da!
なんだいこれ？
What is this?
ちょこのギリギリを守るために特別に作られたモザイク棒です！
A mosaic stick specially made to protect Choco's borderline areas!
特別！？すげー！
Specially made?! Awesome!
特別仕様来た！
A special edition!
モザイク！
Mosaic!
なんとこれ！
Get this!
ボタンでこのモザイクの粗さを変えれるらしい！
You can apparently change the mosaic density with a button!
変えれるの！？
You can change it?!
今めっちゃ粗くなってるから！
It's super rough right now!
あ、本当だ、薄くできる！
Ah, it's true, I can make it thinner!
本当だ！薄ーい！
Really! It's thin!
すげー！
Amazing!
でもなんか粗い方が、むしろいいまであるな、これ。
But honestly, the rougher version might actually be better.
確かに。
True.
隠すやん！
Hiding it!
これ大丈夫かな？
Is this gonna be okay?
でも配信、ね、ちょっと守りますよ！
But I'll protect the stream, okay!
ちょこの配信を守ってください！
Please protect Choco's stream!
守りまーす！
I'll protect it!
がんばります！
I'll do my best!
それでは撮影会、スター卜！
Well then, photoshoot start!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まずはやっぱ全身？
First up, full body?
そうだね～。
Right~.
そうだよね。
Thought so.
普通にこうね、ちょっとポーズ、いつものちょこセンの…
Just a normal pose, the usual Choco-sensei style...
こんな感じ？
Like this?
おお～！
Ooh~!
美しい！
Beautiful!
こうから…
From this...
美しい！
Beautiful!
あ、いいねいいね！
Ah, nice nice!
いや可愛い！
Wow, cute!
もうここちょっとまずいんじゃないの、ここ！
Wait, isn't this part a little risky right here?!
ちょっとまずいかな？
Is it risky?
逆に！逆に！？
Conversely! Conversely?!
え？
Eh?
逆に！？
Conversely?!
ノリノリなんですけど！
She's really getting into it!
まずいかな？
Is it bad?
ちょっと、ちょっとね…
Just a little...
ちょっとここ揺れて…
It's jiggling here a bit...
モザイクが追いついてない！
The mosaic can't keep up!
追いついてない！
Can't keep up!
ちょ、ノエル様頑張って、頑張って！
Noel-sama, do your best, hang in there!
頑張ります！
I'm trying!
こうやってね、こういう感じでね。
Like this, just like this.
じゃあ、どんどん、どんどん…ちょっとジャンプしてもらってみてもらっても？
Then, more and more... could you try jumping a little?
あ、ジャンプ確かにすごいプルンって…
Ah, jumping would definitely make it jiggle...
エイッ！
Ei!
あー！！ダメダメダメ！
Ah!! No no no!
めっちゃ揺れてる！ダメダメダメ！
It's jiggling too much! No no no!
あかんてしょこれ！
This is forbidden!
さよなら、さよなら…！
Goodbye, goodbye stream...!
おいおいおい！
Oi oi oi!
えへっ！
Ehe!
あら～！
Oh my~!
え、ちょっとせっかくだから椅子とかも座っちゃう？
Eh, since we're here, wanna sit on the chair?
お、椅子？
Oh, chair?
うん、椅子ね、ここに…
Yeah, the chair is here...
ありますね。
Here it is.
はーい。
Okay.
椅子！よいしょ。
Chair! Yoisho.
おお、いい！靴も可愛い！
Ooh, nice! The shoes are cute too!
なんかちょっと青っぽいんだね。
They're a bit bluish.
あ、そう、ちょこね…
Ah, yes, Choco's...
そこが赤なの。
that part is red.
あ…えぇっ！？
Ah... Eeh?!
ちょちょちょちょ…まずい、まずいよ！
Wait wait wait... bad, that's bad!
ああ、ありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you very much!
そこがね、赤なの、これ。
That part, you see, it's red.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
すごいね！
Amazing!
そう、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you!
大丈夫？あ、でも中見えてないからね！
Is it okay? Ah, but you can't see inside!
大丈夫です、大丈夫です、セーフです！
It's okay, it's okay, it's safe!
守ってます！チャンネル守ってます！
We're protecting it! Protecting the channel!
じゃあこう、どんどん、どんどん上を…
Then, let's look... higher and higher...
うん、見てもらって…
Yeah, looking at...
あ、いいね！
Ah, nice!
あら可愛い！
Oh, cute!
あ、いいねー！
Ah, that's good!
見えてる～？
Can you see~?
見えてるよ、見えてるよ！
We can see, we can see!
見えてる～！
I can see~!
あ～、かわ、可愛い！
Ah~, cu- cute!
可愛いね！
Cute!
う～ん！
Mmh!
え、ちなみにラミィさん、あれですよ！
Eh, by the way Lamy-san, about this!
この椅子に座って先生ポーズも…
The 'Sensei pose' while sitting on this chair...
あ、先生ポーズ！
Ah, Sensei pose!
撮ってほしい！
I want a picture of that!
先生ポーズってなんだ？
What's the Sensei pose?
こんな感じ？
Like this?
あー！いい！
Ah! Nice!
いいですね、いい、非常にいい！
It's good, good, very good!
やっぱもう、モザイクいらないね、これは！
We don't need the mosaic for this one!
非常に！
Indeed!
本当にいらないのか、これ？
Do we really not need it?
いや分かんない、ちょこセンの魅力が溢れすぎてて！
I don't know, Choco-sensei's charm is overflowing!
いいですね～！
So nice~!
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
え、じゃあ団長もいいですか？
Eh, then can I ask Danchou something?
なになに？
What is it?
お尻フリフリをちょっと、していただきたいんで…
I'd like to see you shake your hips a little...
フリフリ…
Shake shake...
えーっと、そう、後ろ向いてもらって…
Umm, yes, turn around...
後ろ向いて…
Turn around...
白衣越しだけど…
It's through the lab coat, but...
フリフリ！
Shake shake!
あ、いいね！
Ah, nice!
白衣越しだが！
It's through the lab coat, though!
その下に！
Underneath that!
あー！ちょっとその下に！
Ah! Just underneath that!
スカート、結構際どい！
The skirt is pretty risqué!
でもこれ、白衣ってこれ、脱いでほしいんだけど、これ脱げないの？
But this lab coat, I want you to take it off, can't you take it off?
ぬ、脱げるけど…メン限でって言ってた！
I-I can take it off... but I said I'd do that in the Members-only stream!
あ！メン限なら脱いでくれるんですね！
Ah! So you'll take it off in the Members-only stream!
あ、じゃあ…
Ah, well then...
ガニ股…
Wide stance...
あのココ会長リスペクトで、団長ガニ股好きなんで！
Out of respect for Chairman Coco, since Danchou loves the wide stance!
うわー！
Wha-!
はい！
Yes!
ガニ股ー！
Wide stance!
あ、いいね！
Ah, nice!
ガニ股助かる！
Thanks for the wide stance!
ガニ股！
Wide stance!
これちょっと、モザイク！モザイク！
This is a bit... Mosaic! Mosaic!
ちょ、見えてるもんな！
Wait, we can see it!
モザイクお願いします！
Mosaic please!
モザイクが、むず、ここが…
The mosaic is... diffi... right here...
ちょ、やばい！
Wait, dangerous!
逆にやばい！
Conversely dangerous!
やばいやばいやばい！
Bad bad bad!
あーい！
Aai!
ふぅ～…
Phew...
どんどん行こう、どんどん行こう！
Let's keep going, keep going!
えーっと…
Umm...
じゃあ…
Then...
ラストは、やっぱアイドルだからさ、ちょこセン。
For the last one, since Choco-sensei is an idol after all.
アイドル、とびきり可愛いアイドル、お願いします！
Idol, an exceptionally cute idol pose, please!
はーい！
Oka~y!
え、可愛い！
Eh, cute!
やっぱこれわ…
As expected this is...
あ、いいね！
Ah, nice!
ですです！
Yes yes!
あーっつい！顔のアッツイね！
It's hooot! My face is so hot!
たまらんです。
I can't take it.
は〜い。
Ye~s.
おっけー、いやいっぱい頂いた！
Okay, wow, I got plenty!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとう〜。
Thank you~.
いやちょっとね、この続きはちょっとメン限でやらせて頂きますので。
Well, we'll continue the rest in the membership stream.
メン限ではちょっと歌も、撮影会も、
In the membership stream, we'll have songs, a photo session,
シチュエーションドラマもなんと2本やっちゃいます！
and even two situation dramas!
楽しみだね！
Can't wait!
ちなみにさ、なんかタイトルとかあんの？そのシチュエーションドラマって。
By the way, do they have titles? Those situation dramas.
あ、今回のタイトルが、
Ah, the title this time is...
先生と...
With Sensei...
ベッドで...
In bed...
特別バレンタイン！
Special Valentine!
特別...！先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン！？
Special...! Special Valentine in bed with Sensei!?
ってタイトルと、
That title, and...
あと診察室で、
Also, in the examination room,
甘い処方箋を...っていう。
Sweet Prescription... is the name.
あ〜、あま〜い！
Ah, so sweeet!
目線も、ちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて、
For the viewpoint, we'll have the cameraman lie down on the bed,
ちょっとみんなが本当に、
so that everyone really,
本当に見えるように、
can really see it like that,
ちょこが覆い被されるように、
like Choco is leaning over you,
色んな画角で撮っていきたいと思います。
I want to film it from various angles.
楽しみー！
Can't wait!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ということでそろそろお時間が迫ってきたので、
So, since the time is approaching,
ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います。
I'd like to return to the live performance.
そうだった！急げー！
That's right! Hurry!
急げ急げ！
Hurry, hurry!
うわ〜！
Waaah!
は〜い！
Yees!
というわけで、
So, with that said,
この後、二人それぞれ、
after this, the two of them,
ちょっとデュエットしてもらうんだけど、
will be performing duets,
最後に3人でも歌うので楽しみにしといてください。
and we'll sing as three at the end, so please look forward to it.
楽しみー！
Can't wait!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
それでは着替えに行きましょうか。
Then, let's go change.
あ、これ？
Ah, this?
すごーい！カーテン！
Wow! A curtain!
ちょっとカーテンの裏で、
We'll just step behind the curtain,
お着替えしてきまーす！
and get changed!
行ってきまーす！
See you soon!
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
ドロドロ so sweet baby
Melty melty so sweet baby
とろけちゃって Catch me darling
I'm melting, Catch me darling
ピュアピュア ココアふんわり
Pure pure cocoa fluffy
つるつる One Two
Smooth smooth, One Two
なんか眠れない夜には
On nights when I just can't sleep
お散歩 特別パーティータイム
Taking a walk, special party time
ふたりきり (やったー！)
Just the two of us (Yay!)
あの角曲がれば
If you turn that corner,
ベンチしかない公園だよ
It's a park with nothing but a bench
蒸し暑い空気の中
In the humid air,
迷い込むんだ
We wander in
コンビニちょっと寄り道
Stopping by the convenience store
解答アイスじゃなくてこれがいい
Not melted ice cream, I want this
アイスじゃなくてこれがいい
Not ice cream, I want this
官能 お酒ほろ酔い
Sensual, tipsy on alcohol
ウインクでストロング
Strong with a wink
テキュールじゃもう酔えない
I can't get drunk on tequila anymore
ラムで潰してお願い
Wreck me with rum, please
お砂糖はマシマシで
With extra sugar,
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱で溶かして
Melt it with scorching heat
ごくって飲んで
Gulp it down
癖のある私のことを
Take care of me,
大事にしてよね
quirks and all
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
ドロドロ so sweet baby
Melty melty so sweet baby
とろけちゃって Catch me darling
I'm melting, Catch me darling
ピュアピュア ココアふんわり
Pure pure cocoa fluffy
つるつる One Two
Smooth smooth, One Two
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
A slightly lonely way home
ふらふら 特別ボーナスタイム
Dizzy dizzy, special bonus time
手を繋ごう (Yeah Yeah)
Let's hold hands (Yeah Yeah)
大きめTシャツ
Oversized T-shirt,
君に借りた ありがとうって
borrowed from you, saying thanks
匂わせみたいにして
Making it look like a hint
困らせたいんだ
I want to trouble you
コンビニまた寄っちゃって
Stopping by the convenience store again
楽しいもう一本だけの
It's fun, just one more
弱いヤツ
weak one
クルクルリン 混ぜる気
Round and round, ready to mix.
テンパリングが大事
Tempering is important.
熱すぎても飽きちゃうって
If it's too hot, you'll get tired of it.
冷たいのはだめよだもん
And it can't be too cold either.
チョコみたいな私を
Treat me like chocolate,
プレシャスにして扱って
Handle me with precious care.
ビターさんのおかげで
Thanks to Mr. Bitter,
シュワシュワシュワ
Fizz, fizz, fizz.
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach if you don't convey it.
恋してる証拠に
As proof that we're in love,
ここでチューして
Kiss me right here.
夜空のグラスに
In the glass of the night sky,
ヒラヒラこぼして
Fluttering and spilling over.
息もできないくらいに
So much I can't even breathe,
もうだってだってだって
Geez, because, because, because!
恋に溺れて
Drowning in love,
君の熱で溶けたら
If I melt with your heat,
そのまんまで食べてよ
Eat me just like that.
手にベトベトついちゃって
Getting sticky on your hands,
一緒一緒
Together, together.
官能お酒ほろ酔い
Sensual sake, getting tipsy,
ウインクでストロング
Strong with a wink.
リキュールじゃもう酔えない
Can't get drunk on liqueur anymore.
ラブで潰してお願い
Crush me with love, please.
お砂糖はマシマシで
Extra sugar, please,
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink.
灼熱でさ溶かして
Melt it with scorching heat,
ゴクって飲んで
And gulp it down.
クセのある私だからさ
Because I'm a girl with quirks,
君が選ばれたサマーチョコレート
You were chosen, Summer Chocolate.
ドロドロとろりベイビー
Melting gooey baby.
トロけさせちゃってキャッチミーダーリン
Make me melt, catch me darling.
ピュアピュアココアふわり
Pure pure cocoa fluffy.
クルクルワンツー
Spinning One Two!
What's up Japan? Can you hear me?
Is life getting dull?
No money, no job?
Too much bad news?
There is no reason to be down.
It's time to get up.
We have a hot new song.
That's from AKB48.
To make you feel good.
Koisuru Fortune Cookie!
So dance Japan crazy!
あなたのこと好きなのに
Even though I love you,
私には興味ない
You have no interest in me.
何度目かの失恋の準備
Preparing for my umpteenth heartbreak.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
周りを見れば大勢の
If I look around, there are so many...
可愛い子たちがいるんだもん
...cute girls everywhere.
地味な花は気づいてくれない
You won't notice a plain flower.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
カフェテリア流れるMusic
Music flowing in the cafeteria.
ぼんやり聴いていたら
As I listened absentmindedly,
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ
Before I knew it, to the rhythm...
つま先から動き出す
...my toes started moving.
止められない今の気持ち
I can't stop this feeling now.
Come on, come on, come on, come on baby
占ってよ
Tell my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Loving Fortune Cookie.
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future isn't that bad.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには
To call upon luck,
笑顔を見せること
You have to show a smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Heart's Fortune Cookie.
運勢今日よりもよくしよう
Let's make our luck better than today.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't worth throwing away, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A surprising miracle will happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
A premonition that we'll love each other somewhere.
あなたにちゃんと告りたい
I want to confess to you properly.
だけど自分に自信ない
But I don't have confidence in myself.
リアクションは想像つくから
Because I can imagine your reaction.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
性格いい子がいいなんて
"I like girls with good personalities..."
男の子は言うけど
Boys say that, but...
ルックスがアドバンテージ
Looks are an advantage.
いつだって可愛い子が
Cute girls are always...
人気投票1位になる
Number one in the popularity polls.
Please Please Please Oh Baby
私も見て
Look at me too.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Falling in Love Fortune Cookie.
その殻さあ壊してみよう
Come on, let's break that shell.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
先の展開
The future development,
神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know.
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
Tearful Fortune Cookie.
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Without becoming so negative.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
世界は愛で溢れているよ
The world is overflowing with love.
悲しい出来事忘れさせる
It makes you forget sad events.
明日は明日の風が吹くと思う
I think tomorrow's wind will blow tomorrow.
C'mon C'mon C'mon C'mon Baby
占ってよ
Tell my fortune.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Falling in Love Fortune Cookie.
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future isn't that bad.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには
To call upon luck,
笑顔を見せること
You have to show a smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Heart's Fortune Cookie.
運勢今日よりもよくしよう
Let's make our luck better than today.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't worth throwing away, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A surprising miracle will happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
A premonition that I can love you somewhere.
君が好きったら君が好き！
If I say I like you, I like you!
Pure love! Pure love!
あのね乙女は本気出すとすごいんです
You see, when a maiden gets serious, she's amazing.
Want you! いずれ手中
Want you! Eventually in my grasp.
あの手この手でライバルを出し抜くの
Using every trick to outwit my rivals.
全部計算済みレシピ通り
Everything is calculated, just like the recipe.
ギャップだって武器にして
Turning even the gap into a weapon.
上目遣いで見たりして
Looking up with upturned eyes.
酔ったフリで甘えて
Pretending to be drunk and acting spoiled.
常にデッドヒート
Always a dead heat.
ああ！失敗した！
Ah! I messed up!
つまみ食いしたら無くなった
I tasted it and now it's gone.
ブランデーや日本酒
Brandy and Sake.
時にファンキー
Sometimes funky.
苦いのはNGで
Bitter things are NG.
女の子の季節だもん全部
It's the season for girls, after all.
思い通りになってよね
Let everything go my way, okay?
君は私と結ばれます
You will be tied to me.
込み上げちゃうメルティー
Welling up, melty.
誰にも渡さない大戦争
A great war where I won't hand you over.
ときめいちゃいますジェラシー
My heart throbs, jealousy.
それじゃ説得力ないじゃん
That's not very persuasive.
内緒のデート
Secret date.
Sweety Sweety Kiss
甘くていいの
Is it okay to be sweet?
Sweety Sweety Heart
こういうのがいいでしょ？
You like this kind of thing, right?
覚悟いい？なんだもん絶対
Are you ready? I absolutely...
譲らない覚悟です
...have the resolve not to yield.
本気なのです
I'm serious.
目を見て言って
Look me in the eye and say it:
君の気持ち
Your feelings.
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girl's Battlefield.
誰彼と喋ってんの？
Who are you talking to?
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girl's Battlefield.
必死すぎて怖いでしょ？ No!
Too desperate, scary right? No!
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girl's Battlefield.
大丈夫焼かれないもん
It's okay, I won't get burned.
惚れさせたが勝ちです
The one who makes them fall in love wins.
余り物全部食べちゃいな
Eat all the leftovers.
砂糖の量は愛の量
The amount of sugar is the amount of love.
間違えたこれ塩だった
Mistake! This was salt!
幻...
Phantom...
超ドキドキしている
My heart is pounding so fast.
真心込めてラッピング
Wrapping it with all my heart.
自分も本気コーデで行く
I'm going in my serious outfit too.
祈るラブビーム...ジャンプ！
Praying Love Beam... Jump!
何度も試作した
I've made so many trial versions.
予行練習もした
I even did a rehearsal.
弱気になどなるな
Don't get faint-hearted.
大丈夫 自分史上
It's okay, I'm the cutest...
一番 かわいい私なんだから
...in my entire history!
君は私と結ばれます
You will be tied to me.
結ばれる運命なのです
It is our destiny to be tied together.
本命あげちゃう メルティ
I'll give you my true love, Melty.
誰にも渡さない大戦争
A great war I won't lose to anyone.
トキメイちゃいます メルシー
I'm fluttering, Mercy.
それじゃ手と手繋いじゃう？
Then shall we hold hands?
ナイショでと
Secretly...
スキスキ Kiss
Love-Love Kiss.
甘くていいな
It's so sweet and nice.
スキスキ Hug
Love-Love Hug.
そういうのがいいっしょ？
You like that kind of thing, right?
初恋なんだもん
Because it's my first love.
絶対譲らない覚悟です
I'm determined not to give it up.
本気なのです
I'm serious about this.
目を見て言って
Look me in the eyes and say it,
君の気持ち
your feelings.
Pure Love, Pure Love
はーい！ということでちょこ達３人の新曲でしたー！
Yesss! So, that was our new song by the three of us!
イェーイ！
Yaaay!
新曲でしたー！改めまして
It was a new song! Once again...
ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にね
...I sang a collaboration song with Noel-sama and Lamy-sama...
コラボ歌唱した「初恋大戦争」という新曲なんですけど
...called 'First Love Great War'.
今回作詞作曲をMedansy様
For this song, we asked Medansy-sama for lyrics and composition...
そして編曲をYousuke様にお願いいたしましたー！
...and Yousuke-sama for the arrangement!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much!
いや今回のテーマが
So, the theme this time is...
バレンタインの日に
...on Valentine's Day...
３人の可愛い女の子達が
...three cute girls...
１人の男の子を手に入れるために
...are fiercely trying to outwit each other...
バチバチにね 出し抜合おうとするみたいな
...in order to win over one boy.
激ヤミな？テーマ楽曲となっております
It's a super intense? theme song.
いいね可愛い
Nice, cute.
もう３人の声が合わさって
The voices of the three of us combine...
めちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので
...making it a super idol-like song...
ぜひぜひ皆様聴いてください
...so please listen to it, everyone.
聴いてねー
Listen to it!
何回も聴きたいな 聴けるところあるのかな？
I want to listen to it many times. Is there a place to listen?
いやこちらの楽曲はこの後24時から
Well, this song will be distributed starting at 24:00 after this...
2月15日0時からね 各種音楽サイトにて配信されます
...from 0:00 on February 15th, on various music sites.
やったー！
Yay!
そしてね
And...
この配信後すぐに この楽曲のMVが
...immediately after this stream, the MV for this song...
公開されます！
...will be released!
やったー！
Yay!
ぜひぜひ皆様いっぱい聴いて
Please listen to it a lot, everyone...
MVの方にも 感想とかねコメントいただけたら嬉しいかなって思います
...and I'd be happy if you could leave comments on the MV too.
お願いします
Please!
じゃあね２人とも今日はありがとう
Well then, thank you both for today.
お誕生日おめでとう
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう 嬉しい
Thank you, I'm happy.
引き続き頑張ってください
Please continue to do your best.
頑張る！ありがとう
I will! Thank you!
おさらばじゃ！
Farewell!
おさらば！
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そしてここからライブ後半となります
And from here, the second half of the live begins.
まだまだゲストパートとか
There are still guest parts...
なんと最後に重大告知もあるので
...and surprisingly, there's a major announcement at the end...
皆様一緒に楽しんでいきましょう
...so everyone, let's enjoy it together!
それでは次のゲストはこちら
So, the next guest is... this one!
大人なフリして
Pretending to be an adult.
急に会いたいって
Saying 'I want to see you suddenly'...
いつものように準備してる
...I'm getting ready as always.
午前0時過ぎの終電で向かうって返した
I replied that I'm coming on the last train past midnight.
やめときなよって言われても
Even if I'm told 'You should stop'...
また会いに行く
...I go to see you again.
会いたいから
Because I want to see you.
真夏に落ち合う
Meeting up in midsummer,
街の風は少し冷たい
the city wind is a little cold.
慣れないワイン
Unaccustomed wine,
無理やり飲み干してしまっては
forcing myself to drink it all up...
ふらふわ
I feel dizzy.
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if I get hated?
下手にしちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess it up?
少しも残したくない
I don't want to leave even a little bit.
ちょっと期待して
Expecting a little,
ねぇ
hey.
ずっと見栄張って
Always showing off,
ねぇ
hey.
周りばかり気にして生きてる
Living while only worrying about those around me.
ちょっと憂鬱感
A little feeling of melancholy,
でもなんか寂しくて
but somehow lonely.
ああ
Ah,
本当の自分じゃない気がして
feeling like it's not my true self.
いつもわかったふりして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
pushing myself even though it's not like that.
味のしないキスでも
Even a tasteless kiss
やっぱ一番嬉しくて
is still the happiest thing.
取り繕った私は
Am I, who patched things up,
かわいいかな
cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me until I break.
何も消えそうな
It's a love connected by a thread
糸で繋がってる恋だね
that seems like it could disappear at any moment.
私が諦めたらきっと
If I give up, surely
簡単に消えちゃうね
it will easily disappear.
引き止めるにはどうする
What do I do to make you stay?
あの子だったらどうする
What would that girl do?
不器用な指を絡めて
Entwining clumsy fingers.
いつもチェックして
Always checking,
ねぇ
hey.
いい子にして
Being a good girl,
ねぇ
hey.
他の子と比べてばかりいた
Always comparing myself with other girls.
一番見てほしい
I want you to look at me the most.
ああ
Ah,
目の前のあなたは
You, right in front of me,
ああ
ah,
どこか違う景色見てる
are looking at some different scenery.
いつも優しいふりして
Always pretending to be kind,
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
laughing even though it's not like that.
近づけば近づくほど
The closer I get,
心は遠く感じて
the further your heart feels.
少しずつ離れて
Leaving little by little...
きっとわかるよ
surely you'll understand.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me tightly enough to forget.
自分はもっと強いって思ってたよ
I thought I was stronger than this.
サヨナラを言えるのにんな
I could say goodbye, you know...
いつもわかったふりして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
pushing myself even though it's not like that.
ふと見せる優しさが
The kindness you show unexpectedly,
ずっと忘れられなくて
I can't forget it forever.
取り繕った私は
Am I, who patched things up,
かわいいかな
cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me until I break.
突然零れ出した
It suddenly spilled out...
私頑張ったよね
I did my best, right?
いつか振り向いてくれると
I thought that one day you'd look back at me,
思っていたもういいから
but it's fine now.
取り繕った私が
The me who patched things up
剥がれていく
is peeling away.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me tightly enough to forget.
chocolate box
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You always look sleepy.
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
You always look bored.
なんかいつもヤバそうだし
You always look like you're in trouble.
なんかいつもスマホいじってるし
You're always playing with your smartphone.
本当はテンション高いのに
Even though your energy is actually high,
アタイといる時低くない？
isn't it low when you're with me?
なんなん自分ありえなくない？
What is it? You're unbelievable.
嫌い！大嫌い！どうでもいい！
I hate you! I really hate you! Whatever!
だったらボクも言うけどさ
In that case, I've got something to say too.
ちっちゃいことでスグ怒るし
You get angry immediately at small things.
言い返したらスグ泣くし
You cry immediately if I talk back.
ごめんて言っても許してくれないし
You don't forgive me even if I say sorry.
その割一夜が明けちゃえば
But once the night passes,
ケロッとおはようとか言うし
you say 'Good morning' as if nothing happened.
あぁなんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person.
畜生！もう知らないぞ！
Damn it! I don't care anymore!
甘い甘い恋の魔法は
The sweet, sweet magic of love is
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
a secret chocolate with the taste of the universe.
二人
Two of us...
散りばめて彩って食べちゃおうか
Shall we sprinkle, decorate, and eat it?
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love.
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
Strange chocolate that tastes like the future.
温めて混ぜたらきっと
If you warm it up and mix it, surely,
いつかお口に合う味になるの
Someday it will become a taste that suits you.
ねぇねぇちょっといいかな？
Hey, hey, have a sec?
なんで？
Why?
さっきはあのねごめんね
About earlier, um, sorry.
なにが？
About what?
いつもモヤってなるじゃん
I always get so muddled up.
それで？
And?
今日はこれを渡したくて
Today I wanted to give you this.
言葉じゃ足りないからさ
Because words aren't enough.
だから？
So?
受け取ってくれないかな
Won't you accept it?
なによ？
What is it?
一緒にいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being with me.
わっ！
Wah!
なんだよそれ
What was that?
あなたの優しさについつい甘えちゃう
I find myself spoiled by your kindness.
誰よりも近いから素直になれない
Because we're closer than anyone, I can't be honest.
君の一生懸命さついつい忘れちゃう
I find myself forgetting how hard you try.
誰よりも一番大好きなのに
Even though I love you more than anyone.
甘い甘い夢の宝箱
A sweet, sweet treasure box of dreams.
奇跡味のナイショのチョコレート
Secret chocolate that tastes like a miracle.
二人だけのイノベーションを
An innovation just for the two of us,
探し組み立てたら賑わおうか
Let's find it, build it, and celebrate!
苦い苦い日々の化粧箱
A bitter, bitter cosmetic case of days.
世界味の最初のチョコレート
The first chocolate that tastes like the world.
冷めきって割れないように
So it doesn't get cold and crack,
大事に包んで生涯の完成ませ
Wrap it carefully to complete a lifetime.
いつだって
Always,
病める時も
Even in sickness,
どんな日も
Any day,
そうずっと
Yes, forever,
健やかなる時も
Even in health,
手を取って
Taking your hand,
死が二人を分かつまで
Till death do us part.
愛してる
I love you.
僕もそうさ
Me too.
そばにいて
Stay by my side.
そばにいる
I'll be by your side.
なんて嘘かもよ
Just kidding... maybe.
ああそうかい僕も適当に言った
Oh really? I just said it randomly too.
甘い甘い
Sweet, sweet,
苦い苦い
Bitter, bitter.
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love.
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
Secret chocolate that tastes like the universe.
二人だけのデコレーションを
A decoration just for the two of us,
散りばめて彩って食べちゃおうか
Shall we sprinkle, decorate, and eat it?
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love.
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
Strange chocolate that tastes like the future.
温めて混ぜたら絶対
If you warm it up and mix it, absolutely,
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
Someday it will become the happiest taste ever.
いっせーので
One, two, three!
Thank you so much! See you next time!
ねぇ一つだけ聞いていい？
Hey, can I ask just one thing?
私のこと
About me.
会えるかな今日は
Can we meet today?
心が騒いで
My heart is fluttering,
好きと言いたくなった
I wanted to say I love you.
ときめきに踊る瞬間
The moment dancing with excitement.
私のことなど
About me and such,
多分気にしてないのだけど
You probably don't care, but,
ここにいるんだよ
I am right here.
私はここだよ
I am right here!
自信が揺れ動く
My confidence wavers.
嫌われてないかな
I hope you don't hate me.
勢いでとにかく
With momentum, anyway,
挨拶だ
It's a greeting!
やっと晴れたねぱっと晴れたね
It finally cleared up, it cleared up brightly.
そして元気になれ
And become energetic.
おはようの代わりに
Instead of 'Good morning',
背中を叩いてさ行くよ
I'll slap your back, come on let's go!
やっと晴れたらぱっと晴れたら
If it finally clears up, if it clears up brightly,
きっと元気な笑顔
Surely a healthy smile.
なんだか今のこの気持ちが切なくなったよ
Somehow this feeling I have now became bittersweet.
授業は上の空
Daydreaming during class.
遠くを眺めた
Gazing into the distance.
恋って甘いもんじゃない
Love isn't a sweet thing.
違う科目ださ多分
It's probably a different subject.
そわそわしちゃうから
I get restless, so...
動き出そうよ
Let's get moving,
自分らしくね
Just be yourself.
楽しく生きるの
Live life happily,
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle.
言わずに悔やむより
Rather than regretting not saying it,
勇気出そう
Let's be brave.
出そう！
Do it!
ずっと前から うんと前から
From a long time ago, a really long time ago,
来てみたくて待ってた
I wanted to come see you, and I waited.
私から最初に
First, from me...
伝えてしまえ
I'll just tell you,
大好きです
I love you.
ずっと前だよ
It's been a long time,
うんと前だよ
A really long time.
聞いたことに答えて
Answer what I asked.
どんな風に
How...
感じてるの
...do you feel?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything.
楽しく生きるの
Live life happily,
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle.
本当は不安でも
Even if I'm actually anxious,
勇気出そう
Let's be brave.
出そう！
Do it!
ずっと前から うんと前から
From a long time ago, a really long time ago,
来てみたくて待ってた
I wanted to come see you, and I waited.
私から最初に
First, from me...
伝えてしまえ
I'll just tell you,
大好きです
I love you.
ずっと前だよ
It's been a long time,
うんと前だよ
A really long time.
聞いたことに答えて
Answer what I asked.
どんな風に
How...
感じてるの
...do you feel?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love.
光のアロー胸を刺す
An arrow of light pierces my chest.
君を分かりたいんだよ
I want to understand you.
ねえ
Hey...
教えて
Tell me.
すれ違う言葉に
The words we miss each other with,
ちょっとだけの後悔
Just a little bit of regret.
涙こぼれた
Tears spilled over.
忙しい感情
Busy emotions...
鼓動にリンクする
...link to my heartbeat.
チューニング
Tuning...
確かめたいんだ
I want to confirm it.
目的ばっかりとらわれて
Caught up only in the goal,
大事なものが霞んで逃げて
The important things blur and run away.
今日もリスタート
Restarting again today.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love.
光のアロー胸を刺す
An arrow of light pierces my chest.
全部分かりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything.
ねえ
Hey...
聞かせて
Let me hear it.
たった1mmが遠くて
Just 1mm is too far.
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days I ran through,
忘れない忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget,
輝く1ページ
One shining page.
お似合いの二人に
A perfect couple...
なんだか複雑な
...it feels somewhat complex.
気持ちがいるよ
There are feelings here.
初めての感情
This first emotion...
鼓動にリンクする
...links to my heartbeat.
体温計
Thermometer...
生まれた
Was born
高鳴った
Throbbing
自分のこと分からないまま
Without even understanding myself,
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even gave advice to that girl.
胸が痛いや
My chest hurts.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love.
光の矢　胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my heart.
気付いたこの想いは
This feeling I've realized,
もう
Is already...
遅いの
...too late.
あの子の方が可愛いの
She is cuter than me.
知ってるよだけど
I know that, but...
「うまくいかないで」なんてね
"I hope it doesn't go well."
逃げ出したくせに
Even though I ran away.
バカ
Idiot.
君のこと全部わかりたいって思っちゃう
I end up wanting to know everything about you.
これが恋だって初めて気づいたの
I realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい
I definitely want you to look at me.
遅かったけど諦めたくない
It was late, but I don't want to give up.
だって　好きだから
Because I love you.
春に咲いた花が恋をした
The flower that bloomed in spring fell in love.
花は必死に上を向いて笑った
The flower desperately looked up and smiled.
青い夏の蕾も恋をした
The blue summer bud also fell in love.
咲かない花と火薬の匂い
The flower that won't bloom and the scent of gunpowder.
匂い
Scent.
ホントの気持ち言葉にして
Putting my true feelings into words,
大事なこと話せたら
If I could speak about what's important,
今日もリスタート
Today is also a restart.
鈍感な君だから
Because you are dense,
口に出して言わなきゃ
I have to say it out loud.
今君に伝えるよ
I'll tell you now.
ねえ
Hey...
好きです
I love you.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love.
光の矢　胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my heart.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything.
ねえ
Hey...
聞かせて
Tell me.
たぐり寄せて　もう0センチ
Pulling it closer, now zero centimeters.
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days we ran through,
忘れない　忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget.
輝く1ページ
One shining page.
はい！ということで
Okay! So,
ここまでは
up to this point,
アキ様、ロボ子、ござる…に
Aki-sama, Roboco, Gozaru... and,
歌…と一緒に歌わせていただきました
I had the pleasure of singing together with them!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
さてさて
Now then,
ここからは
from here on,
なんと！重大告知が
Surprisingly! Big announcements!
二つあります！
There are two of them!
まず一つ目が
The first one is...
こちら！
This!
ドドン！
*Ta-da!*
癒月ちょこ誕生日記念2026グッズ！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Commemoration 2026 Goods!
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います
So, I'd like to introduce them in a bit more detail.
まずはこちら！
First is this!
ちょこのクッション！
Choco's Cushion!
いやこれね
You know, this one...
いやちょっとちょこの誕生日といえば
Speaking of Choco's birthday,
毎年Nardack先生ありがとうございますということで
I always thank Nardack-sensei every year, and...
今年もNardack先生に
This year too, Nardack-sensei...
めちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト
drew an extremely wonderful illustration...
書き下ろしていただきました！
just for us!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで
Since the theme this time is Valentine's Day,
ちょっとね　ちょこめいとを抱きながら
while hugging a Choco-mate...
ちょっと今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました
I tried making it a chocolate-style cushion this time.
可愛いでしょ？
Cute, right?
サイズ感がちょうど枕くらいになってるので
The size is just about right for a pillow,
ちょっとね　お昼寝の時とか
so for a little nap time or such,
仮眠用に
for dozing off,
すや～ってできる
you can go 'Zzz'...
感じで使えちゃいます
and use it like that!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next is this!
ちょこのちょこ…型！
Choco's Choco... Mold!
今回初めてちょっとね お菓子が作れる
For the first time ever, you can make sweets with this...
なんとなんと ちょこのチョコレート型！
Believe it or not, a Choco chocolate mold!
耐熱も 冷却も あったかいのも 冷たいのも両方使えちゃって
It's heat and cold resistant, so you can use it for both hot and cold things.
ちょっとね ショコラと チョ コ メ イ ト の今回は
This time, it features Chocola and Chocomate...
チョコレート型になっております！
...in the form of a chocolate mold!
ま、マフィンとかね クッキーとか
You know, like muffins or cookies...
あとはまあ普通に 冷やし固めてチョコレート入れたりとか なんか色々使えるからぜひ
Or just simply cooling and hardening chocolate in it. You can use it for various things, so please...
みんなも作ってみてね！
...everyone, try making something too!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
お待たせしました！ ちょこのすやすやぬいぐるみキーホルダー
Thanks for waiting! Choco's Soundly Sleeping Plushie Keychain.
まあちょこと言えばね 睡眠ということで
Well, when you think of Choco, you think of sleep.
超ロングスリーパーのちょこが
Choco, the super long sleeper...
今回はぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなって
...is becoming a plushie keychain this time.
ちょっとすやすやぬいぐるみで 作らせていただきました
I had it made as a soundly sleeping plushie.
まあずっとね 肌身離さず持っていれば いつか「あぁ〜」が聞こえてくるかもしれない
If you keep it with you all the time, you might hear an "Aah~" someday.
そして 今年もございます
And, we have it this year too.
癒月ちょこ書き下ろし台本の 耳舐めASMRボイス！
Yuzuki Choco's newly written Ear Licking ASMR Voice script!
撮りましたよ ちょこのASMRボイス
I recorded it, Choco's ASMR voice.
今回ね 耳舐めの方は ３つございます
This time, there are three types of ear licking.
一つ目が 「とろけかけのチョコレート」
The first is "Melting Chocolate".
いやこちらはね あのちょっと あの皆様がご想像してるより ちょっとあの... あの...
Well, this one is... um, a bit more than everyone is imagining... a bit, um...
エチチかもしれないんですけど
...it might be a little lewd.
まあ配信ではね 絶対にできないボイスとなっておりますので
It's a voice that I definitely can't do on stream.
ぜひともね皆様 ご購入して聴いてみてください
Please everyone, do buy it and give it a listen.
そして もう一つが 「残業後のご褒美デザート」ということで
And the next one is "Reward Dessert After Overtime".
こちらはね ちょことの同棲シチュエーションとなっております
This one is a living-together situation with Choco.
はい ちょこが 残業してきて 帰ってきたときの
Yes, when Choco comes home from overtime work...
んー まあデザートは ちょこなのか 君なのか
Hmm... well, is the dessert Choco? Or is it you?
どっちなんだろうね
Which one is it, I wonder?
まあちょっと聴いてみてよ
Well, just give it a listen.
そしてそして 「年下幼馴染のツンデレバレンタイン」ということで
And finally, "Younger Childhood Friend's Tsundere Valentine".
今回はね 聴いている君たちが ちょっと隣の家のお兄ちゃんになった気分で
For this one, I want you listeners to feel like the older brother next door...
聴いてみてください
...while you listen.
こちらもね 耳舐めボイスとなっておりますが
This is also an ear licking voice, but...
なんとこちら
Surprisingly...
ドMの方は絶対に聴いていただけたら ちょっとニコニコしちゃうんじゃないかなって思います
If you're a masochist and listen to this, I think you might find yourself grinning.
はい
Yes.
そしてそして フルセットをご購入の方 フルセット特典
And, for those who buy the full set, the Full Set Bonus.
今回はなんと初めて チェキ風ブロマイドカードになりました
For the first time, it's a Cheki-style bromide card!
ちょっとこちらね 数量限定で 直筆サイン ＆ 箔押し複製メッセージが入っております
This one, in limited quantities, comes with a handwritten autograph and a foil-stamped message.
カキカキしちゃうよー
I'll be writing them myself!
通常バージョンは 箔押し複製サインと 複製メッセージが入ります
The regular version will include a foil-stamped reproduction autograph and a reproduction message.
そしてね 特典がもう一つ フルセット購入特典として
And there's one more bonus for the full set purchase...
「ヤキモチのぎゅー」と ASMRボイスが入っております
A "Jealous Hug" ASMR voice is included.
こちらはね ちょっとあの 甘々の ぎゅーボイスなので
This one is a very sweet hugging voice.
まあちょっとね 普段あんまちょこ嫉妬しないんですけど ちょっとまあ何に嫉妬してるかは 聴いてからのお楽しみなんですけど
Well, Choco doesn't usually get jealous, but you'll have to listen to find out what I'm jealous of.
ちょっとぜひぜひ ニヤニヤしながら聴いといてください
Please enjoy listening to it with a grin on your face.
ぜひ手に入れてください
Please definitely get it.
そしてそして
And also...
重大告知 ２つ目は... こちら！
Major Announcement number 2 is... this!
不思議ね キミの言葉を聞くと
It's strange, when I hear your words...
なんだか勇気が出てきちゃう
I somehow feel courageous.
…ねぇ、ちょこたち
...Hey, Choco and the others...
もう二度と会えないの？
Can we never meet again?
辛い感情も、孤独な気持ちも
Painful emotions, lonely feelings...
ちょこが全て食べてあげるわ。
Choco will eat them all for you.
ちょことの時間しか いらないって 言って
Say you don't need anything but time with Choco.
ちょこのことをもっともっと、 大好きになってほしい。
I want you to love Choco more and more.
もう一度、会いたいよ。
I want to see you one more time.
ねぇ、もしよければキミに...... ちょこの思い出話、聞いてほしいの。
Hey, if it's okay with you... I want you to hear Choco's memories.
「The Beginning」
12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリース ＆ 連動ボイスドラマプロジェクトスタート
"The Beginning"
12 Consecutive Months Original Song Release & Linked Voice Drama Project Start
3/15 から毎月15日0時 オリジナル楽曲リリース
Original song releases on the 15th of every month at 0:00, starting March 15th.
豪華アーティスト参加
Featuring gorgeous artists.
癒月ちょことあなたのストーリーを辿った 全12話のボイスドラマ
A 12-episode voice drama tracing the story of you and Yuzuki Choco.
「The Beginning」project 始動！
"The Beginning" project Start!
はーい！
Haaai!
2月15日からオリジナル楽曲
Starting February 15th, for my original songs,
12ヶ月連続リリースが決定しました！
we've decided on a 12-month consecutive release!
しかもこちら、なんとオリ曲に
And not only that, but for these original songs...
ストーリー連動のボイスドラマが
a story-linked voice drama...
一緒にリリースされます
will be released along with them!
いやこちらね
Now, about this...
約1話から12話まで
from episode 1 all the way to episode 12,
1曲ずつに連動して
linked one-by-one to each song,
ボイスドラマもあるので
there will be voice dramas too,
ぜひぜひ楽しみに待っててくださーい！
so please, please look forward to it!
そして今回はね
And so, for this occasion,
その記念すべき
that memorable...
1曲目を、これから披露したいと思います
very first song, I would like to perform it now.
それでは聴いてください
Please listen.
キミの秒針
Kimi no Byoushin (Your Second Hand).
戻れないからまた
Since we can't go back, once again...
愛しさが増す
my affection grows stronger.
キミに会いたいよ
I want to see you.
キミから受け取った 壊れそうなストーリー
The fragile story I received from you.
どこまでも広がる 仰いだ空
The sky I looked up at, expanding endlessly.
変わらない毎日も 色のない夢も
Even the unchanging days, even the colorless dreams.
手放して始めようよ
Let's let go of them and begin.
不安な夜を数え
Counting the anxious nights...
泣きながら迎えた朝
the morning I welcomed while crying...
でもいい
but that's okay.
時計の針のように
Just like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち広げた
I spread out the memories we carved.
戻れないからまた
Since we can't go back, once again...
愛しさが増す
my affection grows stronger.
キミに会いたいよ
I want to see you.
二人で温めた 大切なストーリー
The precious story we warmed together.
遠くまで続いた 果てない道
The endless road that continued far away.
疲れたら代わるから そう言ってくれた
You said, 'I'll take your place if you get tired.'
優しさに触れて癒えた
I was healed by touching that kindness.
受け入れてくれたこと
The fact that you accepted me...
忘れない 嬉しくて 満ちた日
I won't forget the days filled with joy.
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain...
架かった虹のように綺麗な
beautiful like the rainbow that appeared.
キミからの言葉 一つ一つが
Every single word from you...
今も宝物
is still my treasure.
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me...
輝ける この気持ち届けよ
I'll send this shining feeling to you.
時計の針のように
Just like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち広げた
I spread out the memories we carved.
戻れないからまた
Since we can't go back, once again...
愛しさが増す
my affection grows stronger.
キミに会いたいよ
I want to see you.
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain...
架かった虹のように綺麗な
beautiful like the rainbow that appeared.
キミからの言葉 一つ一つが
Every single word from you...
今も宝物
is still my treasure.
Is still my treasure.
はーい、ということで！
Riight, so!
みんな、どうだったかなー？
How was it, everyone?
今回の新曲『キミの秒針』は、
My new song, 'Kimi no Byoshin'...
シドのマオ様が作詞、
Lyrics by Mao-sama of SID,
そして御恵明希様が作曲、
and composition by Aki Mimegumi-sama.
編曲...
Arrangement...
そして編曲にはなんと！
And for the arrangement, believe it or not!
加藤貴之様も加わっていただきましたー！
Takayuki Kato-sama has also joined us!
いやー、今回は、
Man, this time,
ボイスドラマ連動企画の第一弾として、
as the first installment of the voice drama linkage project,
ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような、
it's become a track that serves as the theme song for the whole story,
立ち位置の楽曲に仕上がっております。
a key musical piece for the project.
ま、ドラマの鍵となるね、
Well, keep an eye out for the 'seconds hand',
秒針という...
which is a key to the drama...
メタファーにも要注目してください！
Please pay close attention to that metaphor too!
シドさんだけではなく、
Not just SID-san,
このあとね、豪華アーティストの皆様にも、
but a gorgeous lineup of artists after this...
たくさん書いていただいたので、
...have written many songs for me, so,
皆様リリース、お楽しみにー！
everyone, look forward to the releases!
こちらの『キミの秒針』は、
This song, 'Kimi no Byoshin',
各音楽サイトは、ちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、
will be on music sites... there's a bit of a gap, but...
3月15日の0時から、配信予定でございます！
it's scheduled for streaming starting March 15th at 0:00!
ま、ちょっとね、公開まで時間が空くから、
Well, since there's some time until the release,
それまでこの配信、
until then, please watch this stream...
何度も見返してみてください！
...over and over again!
聴き込んでね！
Listen to it a lot, okay?
そしてそして！
And, and!
MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、
The MV will also be released at a later date, so
楽しみにしててくださーい！
please look forward to it!
ということで、
So,
今日のちょこの生誕ライブは、どうだったかなー？
how was Choco's birthday live today?
ま、このあとは、
Well, after this,
すぐに！
right away!
ちょっとね、冒頭... 最初の方でお披露目した、
Like I revealed at the... at the very beginning,
ノエちゃんとラミたんとの、
with Noe-chan and Lamy-tan,
3人の『初恋大戦争』の、
the three of us, 'Hatsukoi Daisensou's...
MV公開があって、
...MV release will happen, and
そのあと！
after that!
メン限で、
in the membership stream,
ちょっとライブと、
a bit of the live,
撮影会の続きとか、
continuation of the photo session and such,
ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れない、
things you can only see in membership,
シチュエーションドラマとかやるので、
like situation dramas, we'll be doing those,
ぜひぜひ、
so by all means,
気になる人は見に行ってくださーい！
those interested, please go watch!
それでは、また後でお会いしましょう！
Well then, let's meet again later!
おつかれーいと！
Otsukareito!
はむっ！
Mwah!